<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Profiles on Dark Science</title>
    <link>http://dark.science/profile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Profiles on Dark Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 22:06:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dark.science/profile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Wetzel</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/daniel-wetzel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 22:06:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/daniel-wetzel/</guid>
      <description>Daniel co-founded Rimini Protokoll in 2000, working in theatre, audio, film and installation. Their work with “experts of the everyday life” is described as groundbreaking and leading the path to new forms of documentary theatre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin Etzrodt</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/martin-etzrodt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 22:04:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/martin-etzrodt/</guid>
      <description>Martin Etzrodt works at the Akasha Foundation, researching the intersection of blockchain and collective intelligence. He has a background in chemistry and biomedical research and was trained in Munich, Heidelberg, Lausanne and Boston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Jaya Brekke</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/jaya-brekke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:55:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/jaya-brekke/</guid>
      <description>Jaya Brekke writes, researches and speaks on authority and control in decentralized systems. Her work contributes to a political understanding of cryptoeconomics, blockchain and consensus protocols. Her PhD is on the political geography of the blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Matthew Difranco</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/matthew-difranco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:53:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/matthew-difranco/</guid>
      <description>Matthew DiFranco is a computer scientist in the Zimmer Lab at the University of Vienna Department of Neurobiology, currently working on visualisation and multimodal sensory/behavioral analysis of C. elegans nematodes using computer vision, machine learning and data science techniques. He is the current Chair of the Marie Curie Alumni Association.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Michalski</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/jerry-michalski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:52:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/jerry-michalski/</guid>
      <description>Jerry Michalski is the founder of REX, the Relationship Economy eXpedition. He is a pattern finder, lateral thinker, Gladwellian connector, facilitator, and explorer of the interactions between technology, society, and business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Clément Renaud</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/clement-renaud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:49:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/clement-renaud/</guid>
      <description>Clément Renaud is a researcher, artist and creative developer specialized in data-intensive projects. He creates new representations and tools based on advanced data workflows. He is member of the Institute for Complex Systems (IXXI) at ENS de Lyon. He lives in Shenzhen (China) and Lyon (France).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miroslav Wiesner</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/miroslav-wiesner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:45:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/miroslav-wiesner/</guid>
      <description>Miroslav is an event curator and designer, co-founder of Mutek.SF, executive director of the Mutek Foundation, and founder of Surefire Productions, working at the intersection of art, music and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max Graef</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/max-graef/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:42:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/max-graef/</guid>
      <description>Max is an audio engineer, the founder of Radioactive.org.uk working with people without radio experience to develop skills and confidence to run their own radio stations and produce radio programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dil Green</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/dil-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:20:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/dil-green/</guid>
      <description>A vocational architect, Dil is now working to develop new tools for human collaboration, understanding and decision making, with a particular concern for public engagement with the reality of complex systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr David Bovill</title>
      <link>http://dark.science/profile/david-bovill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 20:43:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dark.science/profile/david-bovill/</guid>
      <description>Trained as a doctor and scientist, David has worked in many fields - multimedia, publishing, communication, education, performance. Connecting these is a thread of deep concern for designing environments for more effective communication, understanding and decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>